您好，您好，美丽的人，欢迎来到这个非常激动人心的关于自动化课程的章节
Hello you beautiful person and welcome to this very exciting section of the Course all about automating
使用bash脚本和Crohn的任务。
tasks using bash scripts and Crohn.
到目前为止，您一直在学习如何在命令行上一个接一个地执行命令。
Now up until now you've been learning how to do commands one after the other on the command line.
但是，有时您需要完成需要多个步骤的任务。
But sometimes however you want to complete tasks that require multiple steps.
因此，与其每次只记住这些步骤并输入这些步骤，还不如记住这些命令步骤
So instead of just memorizing the steps and entering those steps those command steps every single time
你需要完成那项任务。
you need to complete that task.
相反，您可以将这些命令写入称为bash脚本的文本文件中，然后只需运行该脚本
You can instead write those commands into a text file known as a bash script and then just run the script
再来一次。
again.
当您运行脚本时，脚本中的每个命令都将从
And when you run the script each of the commands in the script will be run one after the other from
从上到下，这样节目将从脚本的顶部开始，然后一直向下
top to the bottom so the show will start at the top of the script and work its way down through the
在途中执行所有命令的脚本。
script executing all of the commands on the way.
好的。
All right.
因此，在本课程的这一节中，您将学习如何创建和运行您自己的bash脚本
So in this section of the course you're going to learn how to create and run your very own bash scripts
但您还将了解如何安排这些命令和后空翻在某些情况下运行
but you're also going to see how you can schedule those commands and backflips to be run at certain
使用一个非常方便的叫做Kramm的日程安排程序。
times using a really handy scheduling program called Krumm.
现在，bash脚本本身就是一个庞大的领域。
Now bash scripting is a whole massive field in and of itself.
因此，这不会是课程的一个过于详细的部分，但我希望在这一部分结束时
So this won't be an overly detailed section of the course but I hope that by the end of the section
您将对糟糕的脚本编程有基本的概念和理解，这样您就可以
you'll have the fundamental concepts and understanding of what bad scripting is all about so that you
可以开始编写您自己的简单脚本了。
can start writing your own simple script.
您还知道如何调度和自动化命令和脚本。
You also know how to schedule and automate commands and scripts.
任何时候你都可以通过使用Kramm书来选择，将这两种技能结合起来将会让你真正设置你的
Any time you choose by using Krumm book and combining these two skills will allow you to truly set your
自动驾驶的工作流程。
workflow on autopilot.
现在，您已经对本节将要介绍的内容有了一个快速的了解，让我们跳到
So now that you've got a quick heads up about what's going to be covered in this section let's jump
我们将在下一个视频中学习如何编写您自己的脚本。
right in in the next video by learning how to write your very own scripts.